<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work on</title><link>/work/</link><description>Recent content in Work on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Skyrock Projects</title><link>/work/skyrock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/skyrock/</guid><description>Skyrock Projects # STEAM Projects for Students age 7-14 # After graduating from Tsinghua in October 2020, I was living in Taipei. I had been going to the hot yoga studio there frequently, and one time I was chatting with another person about how I just graduated and was looking for an engineering job. Someone else overheard our conversation, and it turns out they worked for a startup that was looking for engineers!</description></item><item><title>Accretive Technology Group</title><link>/work/atg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/atg/</guid><description>Leveling up Front-End Skills # Creating ads seen by millions # As a Front-End Web Developer at ATG, my main responsibility was to analyze industry trends and lead the implementation of CRO initiatives. During my time at the company, I had the opportunity to work on several exciting projects that contributed to the success of the business.
Quick stats: ATG is a B2C streaming platform with over 2K white labels.</description></item><item><title>AllTreatment</title><link>/work/alltreatment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/alltreatment/</guid><description>A resource for those battling addiction # Startup Employee #1 # Working at AllTreatment.com was an exciting and educational experience. As an intern, my primary responsibility was to research and write SEO content to help the website rank higher on search engines. I learned a lot about search engine optimization and how to write content that is both engaging and informative.
After I graduated, I was given the opportunity to become the first employee of the company.</description></item><item><title>University of Washington</title><link>/work/uw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/uw/</guid><description>Caput vino delphine in tamen vias # Cognita laeva illo fracta # Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Te at cruciabere vides rubentis manebo Maturuit in praetemptat ruborem ignara postquam habitasse Subitarum supplevit quoque fontesque venabula spretis modo Montis tot est mali quasque gravis Quinquennem domus arsit ipse Pellem turis pugnabant locavit Natus quaerere # Pectora et sine mulcere, coniuge dum tincta incurvae.</description></item><item><title>Boeing</title><link>/work/boeing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/boeing/</guid><description>Caput vino delphine in tamen vias # Cognita laeva illo fracta # Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Te at cruciabere vides rubentis manebo Maturuit in praetemptat ruborem ignara postquam habitasse Subitarum supplevit quoque fontesque venabula spretis modo Montis tot est mali quasque gravis Quinquennem domus arsit ipse Pellem turis pugnabant locavit Natus quaerere # Pectora et sine mulcere, coniuge dum tincta incurvae.</description></item><item><title>Consulting</title><link>/work/consulting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/consulting/</guid><description>Consulting History # Green Air Supply - Jan-Feb 2023 # Green Air Supply is a company that makes nitrogen separators. One of the founders wanted to have a GPT3 chatbot for the 2023 Beverage trade show. I made them a chatbot that would consider their documentation and previous customer interactions to answer any questions a new customer or operator might have about their products. You check out the Bev-Bot here.</description></item></channel></rss>