<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>School on</title><link>/school/</link><description>Recent content in School on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meditation Buddy</title><link>/school/meditation-buddy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school/meditation-buddy/</guid><description>Meditation Buddy # Summary # Meditation Buddy was my thesis for Tsinghua University. I was the creator of the project and saw it through from initial conception to launching and testing with 20 different participants to see the effectiveness of the app.
Meditation Buddy is a meditation app that uses the smartphone camera to assess the user&amp;rsquo;s body position of the upper torso and head. Based on their body position for the last 6 seconds, an inference is made of whether or not they are meditating.</description></item><item><title>BatteREuse</title><link>/school/battgenie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school/battgenie/</guid><description>BatteREuse # Summary # For the launch project as part of the GIX program, the GIX team partnered with UW-spinoff BattGenie to develop a use-case &amp;amp; market entry point for the nascent technology.
The GIX team developed a prototype Energy Storage System (ESS) and Battery Management System (BMS) for Lithium-ion batteries. It included a customer-facing dashboard that went through two rounds of usability testing.
This post is a rehash of our final report and final presentation.</description></item><item><title>Boombox 2.0</title><link>/school/boombox-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school/boombox-2/</guid><description>At me ipso nepotibus nunc celebratior genus # Tanto oblite # Lorem markdownum pectora novis patenti igne sua opus aurae feras materiaque illic demersit imago et aristas questaque posset. Vomit quoque suo inhaesuro clara. Esse cumque, per referri triste. Ut exponit solisque communis in tendens vincetis agisque iamque huic bene ante vetat omina Thebae rates. Aeacus servat admonitu concidit, ad resimas vultus et rugas vultu dignamque Siphnon.
Quam iugulum regia simulacra, plus meruit humo pecorumque haesit, ab discedunt dixit: ritu pharetramque.</description></item><item><title>Deepfake Detection</title><link>/school/deepfake-detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school/deepfake-detection/</guid><description>Kaggle Deepfake Competition # For one of the courses at Tsinghua we had the opportunity to take part in a Kaggle competition. We chose the Deepfake Detection. While we didn&amp;rsquo;t win first, we did get a pretty competitive model!</description></item><item><title>Undergrad</title><link>/school/align/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/school/align/</guid><description>Undergraduate Projects # Undergraduate Research Symposium # Creating a Linguistic Gold Standard for Greek # I worked with the late iSchool professor, Efthimis Efthimiadis, to help parse the Greek language for use in Greek search engines.
Me presenting at the Undergraduate Research Symposium. Look at that young Zach! It was my first real use case for python and learning firsthand how O(n) can impact your code. My initial code took waaay to long to run.</description></item></channel></rss>